Okay, perfect. Like they said, an adjuster will be reaching out to you in the next 24 to 48 hours
to schedule the inspection. The absolute most important part of this process is that I am at
this inspection. Insurance companies do not want to pay out. They are trying to mitigate their losses
after storms. I am there as your representation to make sure you get a fair shake. This basic
agreement backs you as the homeowner by guaranteeing you that your only cost will be your deductible
if we get you fully approved. If it is a partial approval or denial, first we will fight and jump
through the necessary hoops to turn that into a full approval. But if we are not able to get you
fully approved, this contract is null and void and you do not owe us a penny. What is in it for us is
we just want to get to do the work. This agreement commits you to using us if we hold up our end of
the bargain and achieve a full approval. This next form is our claim authorization form. Very simple,
it allows us to communicate with your insurance company. I will be here for the inspection and we
will also communicate with them through email and phone calls so you do not have to be a middleman.
Of course, I will always keep you looped in with our communication by CCing you in all emails and
updating you on any conversations we have. All right, we are all set. Again, the most important
part of this process is that I am here when the insurance company comes out. Ideally, you can have
them call me to schedule that directly. If they call me, great. But regardless, please get the
adjuster information and send that over to me so that I can communicate with them before the
inspection. Thank you, sir. Looking forward to seeing you on the day of inspection. You have my
contact information on my card if you need anything else.